adgorithms.com 2015-06-08

# Adgorithms | Privacy Policy

Adgorithms (“Adgorithms”, “we” or “us”) understands how important it is to keep your private information safely as you interact with our network. This Privacy policy was created to inform you what information we collect when you visit Adgorithms.com (the “Site”) as well as our customers and partners website (“Partners”), and when you use Adgorithms’ solutions to optimize and manage your campaigns (the “Solutions”, and together with the Site- the “Service”).

BY ACCESSING AND/OR USING THE SERVICE (OR ANY PART THEREOF), YOU AGREE TO THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS SET FORTH IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY. IF YOU DISAGREE TO ANY TERM PROVIDED HEREIN, PLEASE DO NOT ACCESS AND/OR USE THE SERVICES AND ANY PART THEREOF IN ANY MANNER WHATSOEVER.

#### INFORMATION WE MAY COLLECT

We collect from your use or interaction of the Service or any part thereof a non-identifiable and anonymous information (“Non-Personal Information”). To put it simply, we have no idea what is the identity of the user from which we have collected the Non-personal Information. Non-personal Information which is being gathered may consist of technical information and behavioral information, as detailed below:  
Technical information:

  * Type of operating system (e.g. Windows, Linux, etc.)
  * Type of browser (e.g. Explorer, Firefox, Chrome, Safari, etc.)
  * Screen resolution (e.g. 800×600, 1024×768, etc.)
  * Browser and keyboard language (e.g. English)
  * Regional settings
  * IP addresses
  * Computer or mobile device configurations and settings and any similar technical data and information
  * Mobile device and OS type (Android or iOS)

Behavioral information:

  * User’s click stream on the Service (i.e. the fact that User has chosen to click on a certain link or access a certain feature on the Service).
  * The activities of the User on the Service, including information pertaining to activities made by the User (e.g. which action was taken on the Service, last login date etc.).
  * Any similar behavioral information.

We may receive from our Partners and ad exchange platforms individually identifiable information (“Personal Information”) such as gender, age range, geographical area and other types of information.  
Such Personal Information will be anonymized by linking it to an anonymous random identifier designated by the ad exchange.  
Adgorithms may collect, when you contact us, your Personal Information including, without limitation, first and last name, address and age, active email address and Geo-location.  
Please note: You are not obligated to provide us with any information by law. You hereby agree and acknowledge that you are providing us with Personal Information at Your own free will.

#### HOW DO WE COLLECT INFORMATION ON OUR USERS

Non-personal Information: When you use the Solutions, we collect Non-Personal information which is derived from information we receive from third party providers, such as Appnexus and other advertising agencies and ad exchange platforms. We also collect Non-Personal Information when you access or use the Site. In other words, we are aware of your usage of the Site, and may gather, collect and record the information relating to such usage. For example, when you use the Site your mobile device tells us your browser type.  
Personal Information: We may collect Personal Information which is provided to us by our Partners and/or third party providers, such as Appnexus and other advertising agencies. We delete such Personal Information. We also collect and store Personal Information which is provided to us voluntarily when any user write and contact us through our Site or through other means.

#### HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION

Your information is used for purposes that include:  
To provide you with and operate the Services, including for statistical and research purposes;  
To personalize the content and advertisements provided to you (including to present offers through advertisers and partners).  
To develop, improve and customize the Service and offerings available through Adgorithms.  
To help offer you products, services or programs that might be of interest.  
Be able to contact Users for the purpose of providing them with technical assistance and support and collect feedback regarding the Service.  
Be able to reply to your online queries or government agencies’ requests.  
To comply with any rule or regulation

#### SHARING INFORMATION WITH THIRD PARTIES

We will not share any Personal Information we collect with any third party. Notwithstanding the foregoing, we may disclose Personal Information in the following cases: (a) to satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process, subpoena or governmental request; (b) to enforce this Privacy Policy and/or the terms, including investigation of potential violations thereof; (c) to detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues; (d) to respond to user’s support requests; (e) to respond to claims that any content available on the Site violates the rights of third-parties; (f) to respond to claims that contact information (e.g. name, e-mail address, etc.) of a third-party has been posted or transmitted without their consent or as a form of harassment; (g) to protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Adgorithms, any of its users, or the general public; (h) when Adgorithms or any of its affiliates is undergoing any change in control, including by means of merger, acquisition or purchase of all or substantially all of its assets; (i) to collect, hold and/or manage your Personal Information through Adgorithms’ authorized third party service providers, as reasonable for business purposes, which may be located in a country that does not have the same data protection laws as your jurisdiction; (j) pursuant to your explicit approval prior to the disclosure; or (k) to cooperate with third parties for the purpose of enhancing Adgorithm’s services and user’s experience.  
For avoidance of doubt, Adgorithms may transfer and disclose to third parties or otherwise use Non-personal Information or information which is linked to anonymous random identifiers or information that is aggregated in a non-identifiable way, at its sole discretion.  
Third Party Software/Services  
While using the Service we may be using third party software and/or service in order to collect and/or process the information detailed herein. Note that these are independent software and/or service inside Adgorithms Service, and Adgorithms does not take any liability about the information collection policies of those software and/or services, or about any kind of issue, legal or otherwise, about these software. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policies and information collection policies of those software before using them.

#### ADGORITHMS USE OF COOKIES AND SIMILAR TECHNOLOGIES

Adgorithms technology utilizes cookies in the delivery of advertisements on our network. This form of advertising is called Re-targeting, and it enhances the web surfing experience by showing the users advertisements that are of interest to them. When a user visits one of our advertiser’s websites, an Adgorithms pixel on that site sets an Adgorithms cookie on the computer of the user. When that user visits one of our partner’s websites, they will identify the cookie and recognize that they previously visited our advertiser’s website. The user will then be shown an advertisement from that advertiser. In this instance, Adgorithms will know the user first visited our advertiser’s website, and then our partner’s website. We will know the user viewed the ad on our partner’s website, and whether or not the user clicked on that ad. This type information is what we use in reporting, and in no way can be used to identify who that user is, or any other online activities of the user outside of Adgorithms network. This information is used strictly for reporting purposes and is not tied to any personal information. You are able to Opt-Out of Adgorithms’s services if you do not want to be a part of future reporting or take part in Re-targeting services from Adgorithms – please see below for instructions on how to Opt-Out.

#### HOW TO OPT-OUT OF ADGORITHMS’S SERVICES

If you wish to Opt-Out of our services, you may do so at any time. Keep in mind that by Opting-Out, you will not enjoy our Re-targeting services. You are free to delete all cookies on your browser, or to have your browser notify you when a cookie is set: simply check your browser settings to do so. By deleting your cookies in this manner, you will disable us, our advertisers and our partners from delivering ads that are targeted to your interests. You will have to clear your cookies each time you visit Adgorithms.com or one of our advertiser’s websites to ensure you are not receiving Re-targeted advertisements. [Another way to Opt-Out is to click this link](http://ib.adnxs.com/optout "Opt Out Adgorithms' services"). When you Opt-Out of Adgorithm’s services in this manner, a cookie will be set on your browser. Adgorithms must maintain the cookie on your browser in order to recognize you as an Opted-Out visitor. You must Opt-Out again if you clear that cookie from your browser, use a different Internet browser, or use a new computer to access the Internet.

#### SECURITY

Adgorithms has established safeguards to help prevent our information from being subjected to unauthorized access or misuse. However, we cannot guarantee that your information will never be disclosed in a manner inconsistent with this Privacy Policy (for example, as a result of unauthorized acts by third parties that violate applicable law or the policies of Adgorithms and its affiliated providers).

#### PROTECTING CHILDREN

Adgorithm’s Services are intended for a general audience. We do not intentionally target minors. Children under the age of eighteen (18) are not eligible to use Adgorithms Services without the participation and supervision of a legal parent or guardian. We do not provide privacy measures designed to protect children when using the Internet unsupervised.

#### CHANGES TO THE PRIVACY POLICY

The terms of this Privacy Policy will govern the use of the Service, and any information collected therein. Ubimo reserves the right to change this policy at any time, so please re-visit this page frequently. In case of any material change, we will make reasonable efforts to post a clear notice on the Site.  
Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective as of the stated “Last Revised” date and your continued use of the Service after the Last Revised date will constitute acceptance of, and agreement to be bound by, those changes.

#### ADDITIONAL INFORMATION AND CONTACT US

Adgorithms may update this Privacy Policy from time to time, and so you should review this policy periodically. If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, you may contact our customer service at customerservise@adgorithms.com.
